[{"answer": "What about my friend", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "N", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I had that dream again", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No, but I have had that one. No, in this one I'm in love..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You've just got to get back on the horse", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Enough to recreate Devil's Tower in", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Aye, you do", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Look, I'm really grateful. Can I offer you some meat as payment? Please, help yourself to some meat", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Trying to be a vegetarian", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No. No. Not for me", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Who for then what", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "So did you and my friend?... you know..", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "With that look, you don't have to talk about it. The grin alone could get you five to seven years", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " To warn you, my friend.  There are just some things you should know, about my friend", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "About her past", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Tell her what", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "We're not lovers", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No. Not officially. I dated a guy for a while who ran a studio", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Actually, that place", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "my friend, if there's anything wrong, I'm here to listen", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Too nice!", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No, he's right!  I'm for shit, I'm one insensitive asshole", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "NO! THERE'S NO MENTION OF THE WIFE! YOU HAPPY!", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I don't think so", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'm going to", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "How do I know you won't reject me again", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " I love you. But you blew it, my friend, you blew it", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I love you", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " Nice? It's more than nice. It's great to meet you. It's fantastic to meet you. I just, I can't tell you how glad I am. my friend. Really. I am", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "The gas station guy? Why would the gas station guy chase us", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What do you mean not paying? You didn't pay him for the gas", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "To The Dry Creek Lodge", "docId": "So-I-Married-an-Axe-Murderer.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Well, I don't want a lift, I really want to commandeer the vehicle. Please just let me commandeer the vehicle", "qsentId": 34}]